Oh, you're home.
I got the stains out, okay?
It's not off-white anymore.
White just comes out different
when it's hand-washed
and sun-dried.
- Why'd you even wash my rags...
- Hey!
That's not a rag!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't tell me you still
wear this!
Hey! Why not?
It still covers what it's
supposed to cover.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here.
[PHONE CHIMES]
"June, can I borrow some money?"
[MUSIC STOPS]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hey.
- [RINGING CONTINUES]
- Your Uncle Dennis is calling.
He's asking to borrow money.
He needs it to pay
for his dentures.
What are you going to lend him?
You don't have any money,
remember?
You lost your job.
- [RINGING CONTINUES]
- It's a sin to turn him down.
[BEEPS]
Hello, Uncle Dennis!
I'm a little short on cash
right now.
Oh, okay.
Just send me your QR code
so I can transfer it.
Bye.
[BEEPS]
I thought you were going
to say no.
I just feel bad for him.
It's hard not having dentures.
But you are
the one who suffers.
You know, if there's
one thing I learned
from what happened to Donato,
it's that money doesn't run out.
But family can be gone
in an instant.
Yeah.
I help them not because
I'm obligated to.
I do it because I want to.
Family is family, right?
I've already got
so little family left.
Why would I be stingy with them?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
They're arguing again.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, sorry!
I got thirsty.
You're just so hot!
Papa Ping and I are okay now.
- Does he love you too?
- Ow!
Isn't it better if you really
get to know each other
before you get married?
Based on the forensic findings,
someone sabotaged Donato.
The yacht didn't sink
by accident.
Be careful.
Most of the time, it's
someone close to the family.